

Junior Web Developer / Blockchain Engineer Specialized in front end development and developing some DApp. Experienced with <u>React</u> library and I am keen on writing some <u>smart contracts</u> deployed on web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, java OOP, node.js, python. Passionate about learning new technology. My strength is equipped with good <u>communication skills</u> and have lots of <u>teamwork</u> experience. During the graduate school I keep learning more techniques about <u>blockchain</u> and <u>k8s architecture</u>.

Leo (Yucheng Lin)

Phone:

+886 989185702

E-Mail:

yucheng2k13@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yucheng-lin-32002b20a/

GitHub:

https://github.com/yucheng880730

Twitter:

https://twitter.com/yuchengggglin

Skill Highlights

- Team work
- Willing to learn new thing
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Enthusiastic
- Leadership

Languages

English – TOEIC 830 Chinese – native language

Experience

02/2021-06/2021

Course Assistant - Artificial Intelligence and Expert System (CCU)

09/2020-01/2021

Course Assistant - Python Programming Language (CCU)

Side Project

- **TodoList:** Web application which backend using nodejs Express framework for CRUD and DB using MongoDB.
- KickStart: A fundraising platform run on Rinkeby test network. DAPP which frontend using React framework backend with smart contract that deployed on Web3js. Routing part using Next.js.
- **Thoughts:** Project with three microservices, two backends and one frontend. This full system run at Minikube locally.

Education

2021-2023

National Chengchi University: Master Degree, Major in Management Information System

2017-2021

National Chung Cheng University: Bachelor Degree, Major in Management Information System

Certificates

- MOEA Certified Big Data Analyst Associate Level
- MOEA Certified Information Security Engineer Associate Level
- Programming program CCU CSIE
- Big Data and Data Science program- CCU MIS